老爸希望我们继承他的遗志
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things, the family business.
在老爸死前说了些
Before Dad died, he told me something.
关于你的事
Something about you.
- 说了什么？- 说我可能会杀了你 萨姆
- What? - That I might have to kill you.
- 这到底是什么意思？- 我不知道
- What's that supposed to mean? - I don't know.
他知道那魔鬼对我有什么计划？
Did he know the demon's plans for me?
我是不是会变成魔鬼什么的？你是谁？
Am I supposed to go dark side? Who are you?
- 求你了 你有危险 - 你叫什么？
- Please. You're in danger. - What's your name?
- 阿瓦·威尔森 - 你是我们其中的一员
- Ava Wilson. - You must be one of us.
- 我们是谁？- 有超能力的人 就像我
- One of who? - One of the psychics, like me.
还有像我们一样的人存在
There are others like us out there.
我们都是什么事的一部分
And we're all a part of something.
我可不是你们中的一员 知道吗？看到这个了吗？
I'm not part of anything. Okay? You see this?
八星期后我就要结婚了
I am getting married in eight weeks.
这事你控制不了
You can't run from this.
而且你也不能一直保护我
And you can't protect me.
但我会尽全力
I can try.
- 也许我能帮上忙 - 你做的已经够多了
- Maybe I can help. - You've done all you can.
回到你未婚夫身边吧 在他身边你会安全的
Go back to your fiancé. You'll be safe there.
保证完事后打电话给我 我保证
Promise me you'll call then. I promise.
阿瓦
Ava.
大部分东西都在这里了
Most of the stuff is up here.
但还是难以相信你要关了这旅馆
I can't believe you're closing, Ms. Thompson.
我父母是在这里订婚的
You know, my parents got engaged here.
我祖父母也是
My grandparents too.
是的 很多人都是
Yeah, a lot of people did.
那些盒子在走廊尽头
Boxes are at the end of the hall.
- 需要帮忙吗？- 不需要 女士 我自己行的
- Need any help? - Oh, no, madam, I got it.
他要拿走我们的玩具了？
He's gonna take our toys?
只是那些你不玩的
Only the ones you don't play with anymore.
你有的玩具已经够多了
It's not like you don't have enough already.
- 婊子养的 - 婊子养的
- Son of a bitch. - Son of a bitch.
- 管好自己的嘴 - 玛吉先说的
- Watch your mouth. - Maggie said it first.
玛吉 你也要管好你的嘴
Watch your mouth too, Maggie.
晚安 塔比瑟
Good night, Tabitha.
喔 上帝啊 是的 你在吗？
Oh, God! Yes, yes, are you there?
请快派人过来 马上
You have to send someone, right now!
救护车 有意外发生
An ambulance. There's been an accident.
他在楼梯上跌倒了 我不知道 他好像…
He fell on the stairs. I don't know. I think he's...
泰勒 不要看
Tyler. Don't look!
不要看
Don't look!
是
Yes.
苏珊·汤普森
Susan Thompson.
快点 快点过来 我…
Just Just hurry! Hurry. I...
不 我不知道 我没有看到
No, I don't know. I didn't see it happen.
[邪恶力量 第2季第11集]
是的
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
谢了 埃伦
Thanks, Ellen.
- 她怎么说？- 没什么发现
What'd she say? - She got nothing.
我正在查我能想到的所有数据库
Me, I've been checking every database:
联邦政府的 州政府的 地方的也查了
Federal, state and local.
没人有阿瓦的消息
No one's heard anything about Ava.
她就是… 像空气一样消失了 你知道吗？
She just-Into thin air, you know.
那你这里有消息吗？
What about you?
没什么进展
No. Same as before.
- 抱歉 - 没事
- Sorry, man. - Yeah.
埃伦有一个消息
Ellen did have one thing.
在康涅狄格州肯尔沃有一家旅馆
A hotel in Cornwall, Connecticut.
在过去的三星期里 发生了两桩怪事
Two freak accidents in the past three weeks.
那和阿瓦有什么关系？
Yeah, what's that have to do with Ava?
这是工作 我是说一位女士在浴盘里淹死
It's a job. I mean, a lady drowned in the bathtub.
接着几天前又一位男士摔死在楼梯上 而且头被转了个180度
A few days ago, a guy falls down the stairs, head turns a complete 180.
这一点都不寻常 不是吗？
Which isn't exactly normal, you know?
我不知道 也许这什么也不是 但我和埃伦
I don't know, Dean, it might be nothing, but I told Ellen...
- 说了会查下这事的 - 你说了？
- ...we'd think about it. - You did?
说了
Yeah.
- 你好象很惊讶 - 是的 觉得这…
- You seem surprised. - Well, yeah, it's just, you know...
不是以前萨姆·温彻斯特的作风 不是吗？
not the patented Sam Winchester way, is it?
- 那应该是什么作风？- 你会先找到阿瓦在哪
- What way is that? - Just figured after Ava...
阴郁的听着伤感的音乐
there'd be, you know, more angst and droopy music...
看着雨中流水的窗户
and staring out the rainy windows.
好了我不说了
Yeah, I'll shut up now.
听着 是我让她回去的
Look, I'm the one who told her to go back home.
现在她的未婚夫死了
Now her fiancé's dead...
那魔鬼又把她弄得不知去向？
and some demon's taken her off to God knows where. You know?
我们已经找了一个月了
We've been looking for a month now...
但还是没有头绪
and we got nothing.
我没有放弃找她 但我也不让其他人去死
So I'm not giving up on her but I'm not gonna let other people die either.
我们要尽我们的所能去救人
We gotta save as many people as we can.
哇哦 那样的态度 对我来说是太过于健康了
Wow, that attitude is just way too healthy for me.
我现在真的不舒服了 谢了
I'm officially uncomfortable now, thank you.
好了 打电话给埃伦 告诉她这案子我们接了
All right, call Ellen, tell her we'll take it.
这里真是太好了
Dude, this is sweet.
我从没在这种地方工作过
We never get to work jobs like this.
哪种？
Like what?
闹鬼的老房子 你知道的
Old school haunted houses, you know?
迷雾 秘密的客人 很娘的英式发音
Fog, secret passageways, sissy British accents.
如果我们走进屋里 就可能会变成佛瑞德和达芙妮
Might even run into Fred and Daphne while we're inside.
达芙妮 我喜欢
Daphne, love her!
嘿 等一下
Hey, wait a sec.
我不知道闹鬼不是唯一的问题了
I'm not so sure "haunted" is the problem.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
你看下这里的图案？
You see this pattern here?
五点的梅花形 是五点咒
That's a quincunx. It's a five-spot.
- 五点咒 - 没错
- Five-spot? - Yeah.
- 那不是咒符符咒吗？- 没错
- That's used for Hoodoo spell work? - Right.
你用血把这里涂满 就能保护你不受敌人攻击
You fill this thing with blood weed, you got a powerful charm.
但这里没有血
Yeah, I don't see any blood weed.
你不觉得这地方
Don't you think this place is a little too...
不太像是下过咒符咒的？
white meat for Hoodoo?
也许吧
Maybe.
- 你们需要什么？- 嗨
May I help you? - Hi.
是的 我们需要一间房住两天
Yeah, I'd like a room for a couple of nights.
嘿
Hey!
- 不好意思 - 没关系
- Sorry about that. - No problem.
恭喜你们 你们可能将成为这里最后的客人了
Well, congratulations. You could be some of our final guests.
听起来有不祥预兆
Sounds vaguely ominous.
不是那意思 我意思是这个月底这店就要关了
No. I'm sorry. I mean, we're closing at the end of the month.
让我猜猜 你们来这里是淘古董的？
Let me guess. You guys are here antiquing?
- 你怎么知道？- 你们看上去就像那么回事
- How'd you know? - You just look the type.
加长的床？
So a king-sized bed?
什么？不
What? No.
不 不 我们要两张单人床
No. No. We're two singles.
我们是兄弟
We're just brothers.
喔 不好意思
Oh, I'm so sorry.
为什么说我们是那样子的？
What did you mean that we looked the type?
你知道 说到古董
You know, speaking of antiques...
你前门旁的那个瓮很有意思
you have a really interesting urn on the front porch.
那个你哪弄来的？
Where'd you get that?
我也不知道 我生下来就有了
I have no idea. It's been there forever.
这是钥匙 马霍·戈夫先生
Here you go, Mr. Mahoggoff.
- 你们的房间是237 - 好
- You'll be staying in Room 237. - Okay.
舍温 你能领这两位先生 去他们的房间吗？
Sherwin, could you show these gentlemen to their rooms?
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
玩古董的？
Antiquers?
我可以帮你搬包
I could give you a hand with that bag.
- 不用 - 好吧
- I got it. - Okay.
- 那这店要关了？- 是的
- So the hotel is closing up? - Yep.
苏珊想开好这店的
Miss Susan tried to make a go of it.
但住店的人却没有以前的多了
But the guests don't come like they used to.
- 实在是太可惜了 - 没错
- Still, it's a damn shame. - Oh, yeah?
虽然看上去也许还不怎么样 但这里曾经也辉煌过
It may not look it anymore, but this place was a palace.
两位副总统来我们这里住过
Two different vice-presidents laid their heads on our pillows.
我父母在这里 我就是在这里长大的
My parents worked here. I practically grew up here.
我会很想这里的
Gonna miss it.
这是你们的房间
Here's your room.
谢谢
Thanks.
你不会那么小气吧？
You're not gonna cheap out on me, are you, boy?
这真是…
What the...?
什么？
What?
这真是很常见啊 为什么这里还一直有人住？
That's normal. Why the hell would anyone stay here?
这里能经营那么长时间真令人惊讶
I'm amazed they kept in business this long.
好了 受害者一号 琼·爱迪生 43岁
All right. Victim number one. Joan Edison, 43 years old, a realtor.
是这个旅店的地产经济人
Handling the sale of the hotel.
受害者二号 拉里·威廉斯
And victim number two was Larry Williams.
- 只是帮忙来搬点东西的 - 有一个关联
- Moving some stuff out to Goodwill. - There's a connection.
他们都是和这店关闭有关系的人
They're shutting the place down.
是的 也许有人不想离开这里
Yeah.Maybe someone doesn't wanna leave.
- 所以用咒符来回击 - 那你认为那个下咒的人为是谁
- They're using Hoodoo. - Who is our witch doctor?
- 那个苏珊？- 好像不太像
- That Susan lady? - No, it doesn't seem likely.
- 她是想卖了这店的 - 那还有谁 舍温？
- I mean, she's the one selling. - So, what then? Sherwin?
我不知道
I don't know.
但最棘手的事是 为什么这么多人都认为我们是断背的
The most troubling question is, why do they assume we're gay?
你看上去很壮
Well, you are kind of butch.
觉得你精力过人
I think you're overcompensating.
大概吧
Right.
嘿
Hey.
看这里 又一个咒符
Look at that. More Hoodoo.
- 你好 - 嘿
- Hi there. - Hi.
- 你们的房间没问题吧？- 蛮好 蛮好
- Everything okay with your room? - Yeah.yeah.
- 一切都很好 - 这就好
- Yeah, everything's great. - Good.
我打包正打到一半
Well, I was just in the middle of packing, so...
那些是古董娃娃吗？
Hey, are those antique dolls?
我们其实就是为这来的
Because this one. This one, he's
他是个狂热的娃娃收集者 是吧？
He's got a major doll collection back home. Don't you?
- 非常喜欢 - 非常喜欢
- Big time. - Big time.
我们能进房间看看吗？
Yeah. You think he could We could come in and take a look?
- 我不知道 - 求你了？
- I don't know. - Please?
他爱这些玩意了 他可能不会告诉你这些
He loves them. He won't tell you.
但是他很喜欢为他的娃娃打扮
He always dressing them up in tiny outfits...
你让她看吧 这会让他很开心的
and you'd make his day. She would. Huh? Huh?
这是真的
It's true.
- 那好进来吧 - 好的 好的
- Okay, come on in. - All right. All right.
哇喔
Wow.
有很多娃娃
This is a lot of dolls.
她们很漂亮 一点也不觉得恐怖
And they're nice, you know, they're not super creepy at all.
我觉得她们有点恐怖
I suppose they are a little creepy.
但她们一直存放在这个家里
But they've been in the family forever.
对她们总会有一些感情的
Lot of sentimental value.
这是什么？
What is this?
- 这家旅店？- 是的 仿真的 一个客人做的
- The hotel? - That's right. Exact replica, custom-built.
他的头被折了
His head got twisted around.
怎么会这样？
What happened to it?
大概是泰勒干的吧
Tyler, probably.
妈咪 玛吉又不乖了
Mommy! Maggie's being mean.
泰勒 告诉她要乖点？
Tyler, tell her I said to be nice, okay?
嘿 泰勒 我看见了你折坏了你的娃娃 需要我帮你修理吗？
Hey, Tyler. I see you broke your doll. You want me to fix it?
不是我做的
I didn't break it.
我看见时已经是这样了
I found it like that.
- 喔 大概是玛吉做的 - 不 我们俩都没做过
- Oh. Maybe Maggie did it? - No. Neither of us did it.
祖母见到娃娃坏了肯定会生气的
Grandma would get mad if we broke them.
- 泰勒她不会生气的 - 祖母？
Tyler, she wouldn't get mad. - Grandma?
罗斯祖母 这些都是她的玩具
Grandma Rose. These were all her toys.
真的吗？罗斯祖母现在在哪呢？
Really? Where is Grandma Rose now?
楼上她的房间里
Up in her room.
我很想和罗斯谈一下 这些令人难以置信的娃娃
You know, I'd really love to talk to Rose about her incredible dolls.
不行
No.
我想
I mean...
这不太行 我母亲病的很重
I'm afraid that's impossible. My mother's been very sick...
她不会和来客交谈
and she's not taking any visitors.
你怎么看？娃娃 下咒
What do you think? Dolls? Hoodoo?
神秘的祖母
Mysterious shut-in Grandma?
娃娃经常被用来下咒符咒发
Well, dolls are used in all kind of Voodoo and Hoodoo...
就像诅咒和咒语一样
like curses and binding spells and-
也许我们发现了那个下咒之人
Maybe we found our witch doctor.
我去查下那祖母
I'll go see what I can dig up on Booming Granny.
你上网看看有什么小道消息和怪事
You get on-line, check old obits, freak accidents.
- 看她以前是不是也对人不轨过 - 好的
- See if she's whacked anybody. - Right.
不要上什么黄色网站 那可不是我说的"不轨"
Don't go surfing porn, that's not the kind of whacking I mean.
我想问一下
I've been meaning to ask.
你们计划如何改建这里？
What sort of renovations are you planning?
他们没告诉你吗？
They never told you?
告诉我什么？
Told me what?
汤普森小姐 我们计划把这里拆毁
Ms. Thompson, we plan on demolishing the hotel.
我知道了
Oh. I see.
不好意思
Excuse me.
再次感谢你
Thank you again.
发生了什么？
What happened?
女佣在换床单位时 发现他
The maid went in to turn down the sheets, and he was just...
- 被吊在那儿了 - 太糟了 他是客人吧？
- ...hanging there. - That's awful. He was a guest?
他是为买这个店的公司工作的
He worked for the company that bought the place.
- 我真想不通 - 什么？
- I don't understand. - What?
这里的坏运太多了
Had a lot of bad luck around here.
听着如果你想退房 我可以退钱给你
If you'd like to check out, I'll give you a full refund.
不用 谢了 我没那么容易被吓倒
No, thanks. I don't scare that easy.
又有个受害者 在房间里面上吊死了
There's been another one. Some guy hung himself in his room.
我看见了
Yeah. I saw.
我们要快点查出这事
We gotta figure this out and fast.
对那祖母 你有什么发现？
What'd you find out about Granny?
你真会指挥人
You're bossy.
什么？
What?
你真会指挥人
You're bossy.
你很矮
And short.
你醉了？
Are you drunk?
是的 那又怎么样？呆子
Yeah. So? Stupid.
你在想什么？我们还在查案子
Dude, what are you thinking? We're working a case.
那个上吊的人
That guy who hung himself.
- 我却不能救他 - 你在说什么鬼话？
- I couldn't save him. - What are you saying?
- 你又不知道 你什么都做不了 - 这不是借口 迪恩
- You couldn't have done anything. - That's an excuse, Dean.
我本该找到方法去救他的
I should've found a way to save him.
我也本该救了阿瓦的
I should've saved Ava too.
即使你这么说 也救不了所有的人
You can't save everyone, even you said that.
不 迪恩 你不明白的
No, Dean! You don't understand.
我救的人越多 我就越能改变
The more people I save, the more I can change.
- 改变什么？- 我的命运 迪恩
- Change what? - My destiny, Dean!
好吧 睡觉时间到了 来吧 大野人
All right, time for bed. Come on, Sasquatch.
- 来吧 我需要你看着我 - 我会的
- Come on.I need you to watch out for me. - I always do.
不 不 不 不是的 你得看着我
No, no, no! You have to watch out for me.
好吗？
All right?
如果我变成了什么 我不愿成为的东西
And if I ever turn into something that I'm not...
- 你得杀了我 - 萨姆
- ...you have to kill me. - Sam.
迪恩 是爸爸告诉你的 你一定要
Dean, Dad told you to do it. You have to.
是的 但老爸很混
Yeah? Well, Dad's an ass.
他不该说任何事的
He never should've said anything. You don't do that.
- 你不该和你的孩子说那种废话 - 不 他说的很对
- You don't lay that crap on your kids. - No, he was right to say it.
谁知道我会变成什么？
Who knows what I might become?
看看现在 我周围的人都死了
Even now, everyone around me dies.
我不是没死吗？
Yeah, well, I'm not dying, okay?
你也是啊 来吧 坐下来
And neither are you. Come on, sit down.
不 求你了 迪恩 你是唯一一个可以做这事的人
No, please, Dean, you're the only one who can do it.
- 答应我 迪恩 求你了 - 别这么说
- Promise. Dean, please. - Don't ask that of me.
你得向我保证
You have to promise me.
我保证
I promise.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你
Thank you.
找到什么古董了吗？
Find any good antiques?
没有 只有些烦心的事
No. No. Got distracted.
来喝一杯吧
Have a drink.
好的 谢谢
Yeah. Thanks.
这么说那个人
So poor guy.
他自杀了？
Killing himself.
这种事最近老是发生
That kind of thing seems to be going around lately.
是啊 是啊 以前的我也听说了
Yeah, yeah. I heard about the other ones.
这更像是这间旅馆被诅咒了什么的
It's almost like this hotel is cursed or something.
如果人们只记得那些
Every hotel has its spilled blood.
在他们所住房间发生过的事的话 你会发现
If people only knew what's gone on in some of those rooms...
每个旅馆都有自己的血案
they've checked into...
你对这间旅馆很熟 是吧？
You know a lot about the place?
连这里的每个钉子都熟
Down to the last nail.
我很想听故事
I'd love to hear some stories.
孩子 你不该和一个老人说这话
Boy, you should never say that to an old man.
这是苏珊小姐和她的母亲罗斯
This is little Miss Susan and her mother, Rose.
快乐时光啊
Happier days.
她们现在不快乐吗？
They're not happy now?
要你离开唯一的家的话 你会快乐吗？
Well, would you be, leaving the only home you ever knew?
我不知道 我从没有过一个
I don't know. I never really knew one.
这里是罗斯的家
Well, this is Rose's home.
她在这住了快一个世纪了
It's been in the family over a century.
这里本来是家族资产
Used to be the family estate.
但现在她却命在旦夕
And now she gets to live in some senior living graveyard...
而他们要把这里推倒了
and they tear this place down.
那太糟了
That's too bad.
- 我听说罗斯生病了 - 是的
- I hear Rose isn't feeling well either. - No, she isn't.
她怎么了？
What's wrong with her?
这不是我该说的
It's not my business to say.
这个是谁？
Who's this?
那是
That's Rose.
小时候的罗斯
When she was a little girl.
和她一起的是谁？
Who's that with her?
那时她的保姆玛丽
That's her nanny, Marie.
她照顾罗斯的时间比罗斯的生母还多
She looked after Rose more than her own mother.
感觉如何 萨姆？把威士忌酒和蒸馏酒混着喝
How are you feeling, Sammy? I guess mixing whiskey and Jager...
不是个好主意吧？
wasn't such a gangbuster idea, was it?
我猜你一定不记得昨晚的事了 是吧？
I'll bet you don't remember a thing from last night, do you?
不 我还可以喝龙舌兰酒
I can still taste the tequila.
你知道吗 有一种很好的治疗宿醉的方法
You know there's a really good hangover remedy.
用脏烟缸装的肥猪肉三明治
It's a greasy pork sandwich served in a dirty ashtray.
- 哦 我恨死你了 - 我知道的
- Oh, I hate you. - I know you do.
嘿 原来祖母罗斯还是孩子的时候
Hey, turns out when Grandma Rose was a tyke...
她有个戴着咒符教项链的黑人保姆
she had a Creole nanny who wore a Hoodoo necklace. Ugh.
- 所以你觉得是她教罗斯的？- 是的
- So you think she taught Rose Hoodoo? - Yes, I do.
好吧
All right.
我想是时候和罗斯谈谈了
I think it's time we talk to Rose.
哦 你得先刷刷牙
You need to brush your teeth first.
有人吗？
Hello?
苏珊？
Susan?
- 没人吧？- 嗯
- Clear? - Mm-hm.
汤普森夫人？
Mrs. Thompson?
罗斯？
Rose?
你好 汤普森夫人 我们不是来害你的 没事的
Hi, Mrs. Thompson, we're not here to hurt you, it's okay.
罗斯？
Rose?
迪恩 这个女人中风了
This woman's had a stroke.
是的 但是咒符是要用手做出来的
Yeah, but Hoodoo's hands-on.
你得做药 念咒 做个祭坛
You gotta mix herbs and chant, build an altar.
- 所以不可能是罗斯 - 也许不是咒符
- So it can't be Rose. - Heck, maybe it's not even Hoodoo.
她可以装病的
You know, she could be faking.
那你要怎么做 用木棍去戳她？
Yeah, what do you wanna do, poke her with a stick?
伙计 你不会用木棍去戳她吧
Dude, you're not gonna poke her with a stick.
到底怎么了？你们在这里做什么？
What the hell? What are you doing in here?
门开着 我们只是和罗斯谈谈
The door was. We wanted to ask Rose
看看她 她都被吓坏了
She's scared out of her wits.
你们给我滚出旅馆 否则我就报警了
I want you out of my hotel in two minutes or I'm calling the cops.
到你了
Your turn. Eightsies.
你开始打包了吗？
Have you started packing yet?
- 没有 - 为什么？
- No. - Why not?
- 我不想搬家 - 我知道 但我们必须走
- I don't wanna move. - Yes, I know. But we have to.
- 但是玛吉说不允许我们走 - 是的
- Maggie says we're not allowed to. - Yeah.
泰勒 够了
Tyler, enough.
玛吉是你想象出来的
Maggie is imaginary.
你够大了不该有想象中的朋友了 我已经不想装下去了
You're too old to have an imaginary friend and I'm done pretending.
我不喜欢她
I don't like her.
- 我可以帮你搬箱子 - 我来就好了 舍温 谢谢
- I could lug those boxes for you. - I got it, Sherwin, thanks.
好吧
Okay then.
待会见
See you later.
- 你还好吗？- 是的
- You okay? - I think so.
快点 快点 我们快进去 快走
Come on, come on, let's get inside. Let's go. Come on.
- 威士忌 - 好的
- Whiskey. - Sure.
我知道这种感受
I know the feeling.
到底出了什么事了？
What the hell happened out there?
- 你想知道真相吗？- 当然了
- You want the truth? - Of course.
起先我们以为是有人在下咒
First we thought it was some sort of a Hoodoo curse.
但是不是
But that out there?
那里面肯定有个鬼魂在
That was definitely a spirit.
给你
Here.
你们疯了
You're insane.
有人说过
It's been said.
我很抱歉 苏珊 但我们没有时间和你解释了
I'm sorry, we don't exactly have time to ease you into this.
我们想知道你母亲是什么时候中风的
But we need to know when your mother had the stroke.
- 那有什么… - 快点回答
- What's that have to do with? - Answer the question.
大约一个月前
About a month ago.
就在血案开始前 明白了吗？
Right before the killings began. See?
所以罗斯不是用咒符来害人的
What if Rose was working Hoodoo...
而是用来保护别人的？
but not to hurt anyone, to protect them?
她用瓮来阻挡鬼魂的
She was using the urns to ward off the spirit.
- 中风后她就不能再做了 - 真不敢相信
- Till her stroke. She couldn't anymore. - I don't believe this.
听着 那辆车不是自己向你撞来的
Listen, that car didn't try to run you down by itself, okay?
我是说 虽然看起来是 但是是被鬼魂所操纵的还是算了
I mean it did, technically, but the spirit can-Forget it.
信不信由你 你和你的家人现在很危险
Believe what you want. You and your family are in danger.
你得把大家都撤出去
All right? You need to clear everybody out:
你的员工 你的母亲 你的女儿们 每个人
Your employees, your mother, your daughters, everyone.
我只有一个女儿
I only have one daughter.
- 一个？- 我以为泰勒还有个叫玛吉的姐姐
- One? - Tyler had a sister named Maggie.
玛吉是她想象出来的
Maggie's imaginary.
泰勒在哪？
Where's Tyler?
她将和我在一起
She's going to stay here with me.
你阻止不了我的
And you can't stop me.
你什么也做不了
There's nothing you can do about it.
玛吉 不要 你不应该来打扰祖母的
Maggie, don't. You're not supposed to bother Grandma.
我知道的
I know.
来吧 我们一起玩吧
Come on. Let's play.
- 我们要玩茶会吗？- 我们会很多的茶会
- Can we have a tea party? - We can have lots of tea parties.
一直到永远 永远
Forever and ever and ever.
泰勒
Tyler?
哦 我的天哪 泰勒
Oh, my God. Tyler.
泰勒
Tyler?
她不在这里
She's not here.
苏珊 你对玛吉了解多少
Susan. Tell us what you know about Maggie.
不是很多或 在我妈生病后 泰勒就开始和她说话了
Tyler's been talking about her since Mom got sick.
好吧 你认识有同样名字的人吗？
Okay. Did you ever know anyone by that name?
- 没有 - 想想 想想
- No. - Think.Think.
曾经住在这里的 也许已经死了的
Could be someone that lived here. Passed away.
我的天哪 我母亲有个姐姐就叫玛格丽特
My God, my Mom had a sister named Margaret.
她很少提起她
Barely spoke about her.
玛格丽特是不是很小就死在这里了？
Did she die here when she was a kid?
是的 她是淹死在游泳池里的
She drowned in the pool.
快来
Come on.
我不想在这上面 我很害怕
I don't like it up here. I'm scared.
没事的
It's okay.
你只要跳下去就行了
All you have to do is jump.
- 我不会游泳 - 我知道
- I can't swim. - I know.
但是不会痛的 我保证
But it won't hurt, I promise.
之后我们就能永远在一起了
And then we can be together. Forever.
再没人会来打搅了
And no one will bother us.
你为什么不跟我和妈咪一起搬走呢？
Why don't you just come with me and Mommy?
因为我离不开这里 而你离不开我
Because I can't leave here. And you can't leave me.
求你了 我不想孤独一人
Please? I don't want to be alone.
泰勒
Tyler.
- 泰勒 - 快呀
- Tyler. Come on.
妈咪
Mommy.
- 有其他入口吗？- 后面
- Is there another entrance? - Around back.
好的 我们走
All right. Let's go.
继续砸门
Keep working.
很快就结束了
It'll all be over soon.
退后
Stand back.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
玛格丽特
Margaret.
哦 谢天谢地 谢天谢地
Oh, my God, thank God.
妈咪？是的 宝贝 我就在这里
Mommy. Yeah, baby. I'm here.
泰勒 你看到玛吉了吗？
Tyler, do you see Maggie anywhere?
没有 她走了
No, she's gone.
妈咪
Mommy.
你真的为我那么做？
You'd really do that for me?
是的
Yes?
如果你做到了 我就放他们一马
If you did, I'd let them go.
但是我不明白
But I don't understand.
你抗拒了我这么久
You kept me away for so long.
我还以为你不再爱我了
I thought you didn't love me anymore.
好吧
Okay...
小妹妹
little sister.
别担心 亲爱的
Don't worry, honey.
我们一会儿就走 只要带上外婆就走
We're leaving in two minutes, we just gotta get Grandma.
我不明白了 玛吉就这么停手了？
I don't get it. Did Maggie just stop?
- 看起来是的 - 她到底去哪了？
- Seems like it. - Where the hell did she go?
救护人员说是另一次中风导致的
The paramedics said it was another stroke.
你觉得
You think...
玛格丽特和这事有关系吗？
Margaret could've had something to do with it?
- 我们不知道 - 但是 有可能
- We don't know. - But it's possible.
是的
Yeah.
苏珊 我很抱歉
Susan, I'm sorry.
我的天 你没有什么要道歉的
My God, you have nothing to apologize for.
你们已经尽力了
You've given me everything.
- 可以走了吗 小姑娘？- 是的
- Ready to go, kiddo? - Yeah.
泰勒 你确定玛吉不在周围了？
You're sure Maggie's not around anymore?
是的 我能看见她
I'm sure. I'd see her.
我想不管是什么事都已经结束了
Well, I guess whatever's going on must be over.
你们照顾好自己 好吗？
You two take care of yourselves, all right?
谢谢你
Thank you.
是的
Yeah.
你们两都是
Both of you.
我还以为你可以走桃花运呢 伙计
I think you could've hooked up some MILF action there, bud.
- 说真的 我觉得她喜欢你 - 是的 那是她想要的
- I'm serious, I think she liked you. - Yeah, that's all she needs.
你救了妈妈 又救了女儿 干得不错 你知道吗
Well, you saved the mom, you saved the girl, not a bad day.
我本可以一个人搞定的 但是我不想你觉得自己没用
I could have saved them myself but I didn't want you to feel useless.
好了 谢谢了
All right. I appreciate it.
能恢复状态感觉不错吧？
Feels good getting back in the saddle, doesn't it?
是的
Yeah.
是的 的确
Yeah, it does.
但是这不代表 我们昨晚说的就不算了 迪恩
But it doesn't change what we talked about last night, Dean.
我们昨晚说了很多
We talked about a lot of things last night.
- 你知道我指的是什么 - 当时你喝醉了
- You know what I mean. - You were wasted.
但是你没有
But you weren't.
而且你保证过的
And you promised.
2 3 4 5 6 7
Two, three, four, five, six, seven...
8 9 10 11 12…
eight, nine, 10, 11, 12...
13 14 15 16…
13, 14, 15, 16...
17, 18...
34 35 36 37…
34, 35, 36, 37...